

302-304-1374 andriamooredesigns@gmail.com www.https://andria-portfolio.pages.dev/#/

### SUMMARY

Hi, I am Andria Moore, a brand strategist and designer. I have experience with designing brands from start to finish. From designing logos, business cards, to social media advertisements I am here to take your business to the next level. I love working in a team as well as independently, I also have experience working with other designers, programmers, and copywriters. I have excellent research, technical, and problem-solving skills as well as detail-oriented and able to learn new concepts quickly.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Graphic Design Intern**

BestLogic Staffing / Rocky Hill, CT / May 2023 - August 2023

- I have successfully created graphics for new companies, including websites, logos, posters, apparel, and other marketing materials using the Adobe Suite
- I have collaborated with internal teams on project briefs to ensure the timely delivery of projects
- I designed three book covers that were selected for publication

# **Graphic Designer/ Marketing Specialist**

Fraim Center for Active Adults / Wilmington, De / August 2020 - April 2022

- I implemented successful marketing tactics to enhance the company's objectives through targeted social media campaigns
- I taught weekly technology classes to seniors
- I redesigned their website using Wix to enhance the company's look and feel

#### **Social Media Manager**

deeR client Hair Salon / Wilmington, De / May 2016 - January 2021

- I reviewed industry trends and analyzed competitors' activities to generate fresh ideas for content creation
- I organized events for the company, such as a haircut-a-thon, to showcase the company's services
- Assisted with scheduling appointments for clients and visitors
- Redesigned and maintained the company website

## **SKILLS**

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Acrobat)
- Proficient in image manipulation
- Exceptional abilities to create high quality material for branding
- Ability to create great marketing tactics

## **EDUCATION**

- Bachelor of Arts: Graphic Design
- Wilmington University | New Castle, DE | August 2023
- [2020-2023] Dean's List
- [3.97] GPA